



FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I'm frontend developer with experience in creating SPA using React, TypeScript, JavaScript,

I am improving my English, studying new technologies and solve tasks on Codewars. Ready to consider project work and full-time employment. Open for your suggestions.

CONTACT



kisselileon@gmail.com



+375 33 619-50-51



Gomel, Belarus

SKILLS

REACT / REDUX / THUNK
JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT
AXIOS / REST API
HTML / CSS / MATERIAL UI
UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
GIT / GITHUB

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022
IT-INCUBATOR
FRONTEND DEVELOPER (JS/TS, REACT, REDUX)

2009 - 2015

FRANCISK SKORINA GOMEL STATE UNIVERSITY

AUTOMATED INFORMATION PROCESSING SYSTEMS

2002 -2006

GOMEL STATE ENGINEERING COLLEGE

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SOFTWARE

LANGUAGE

English (Intermediate)
Russian (Native)
Belarusian (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

2011 - 2021

System Administrator

Information and Computing Center of the Ministry of Finance

Domain: Finance

SCSS, HTML.

Project: Services in automation, development and

maintenance of software systems.

Responsibilities: Software maintenance (updating, troubleshooting) MS SQL Server (backup, configuration) Windows Server Administration Administration and configuration of network equipment

2007-2008

Client service specialist

Media Line

Responsibilities: Provision of services on promotion of sites in search engines, purchase of sites, placement of advertising links and banners.

MY PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO
LEARNING CARDS
TODO LIST